(Sheldon:)Tonight I'll be watching
a show rated M.A.,
(Sheldon:)and that stands for
"Mature Audiences," buster.
(Penny:)All right, you would
think "the only adult"
(Penny:)wouldn't let something silly
ruin our entire night.
(Leonard:)And I'd think you'd understand
why I'm annoyed.
(Sheldon:)All this could be avoided if
you'd just come to the meeting.
(Leonard:)I don't want to.
(Sheldon:)Oh, it's just a meeting.
(Sheldon:)One simple meeting.
Stop saying "meeting"!
♪ Meeting, meeting, bo-beeting ♪
♪ Banana-fana, fo-feeting ♪
♪ Fee-fi mo-meeting... ♪
(Amy:)I brought
my famous spinach dip.
Yo, Amy, just one second.
♪ Meeting. ♪
(Howard:)I'm not sure if I'm hoping
for a boy or a girl.
(Howard:)I mean, if it's a boy,
(Howard:)I'm gonna have to teach him
to play catch.
(chuckles) Which means
I'm gonna have to Google
"How to play catch."
(Howard:)If it's a girl, I mean...
(Howard:)they're so innocent and...
you know how guys are.
(Raj:)Totally, guys are the worst.
(Raj:)I mean, look at me.
(Raj:)I let Emily make me a frittata
(Raj:)and I kept the leftovers
in Claire's fridge that night.